자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)
The vic is Ross Neddy.
피해자 이름은 로스 네디입니다
Ex-con. Spent a couple years
in Jean for domestic assault.
전과자인데 가정 폭력으로
감옥에서 2년 복역했다가
Just got paroled.
얼마 전에 가석방했답니다
Shop foreman says he's only
been working here a few days.
폐차장 주임 말로는
여기서 일한 지 며칠 안 됐다고 하네요
Out of the frying pan into the fire.
프라이팬을 탈출해서는
불에 뛰어들게 된 꼴이군요
He is a crispy critter.
폭삭 튀겨졌네요
I'd say the point of origin was him.
발화 지점은 이 사람일 겁니다
He should have stayed in prison.
감옥에 그냥 있는 게 나았겠네요
Sloppy shop.
가게가 너저분하군요
This whole place is a fire hazard.
화재의 원인이 될 만한 게 널려 있어요
Okay if I move him out?
이제 시체를 옮겨도 될까요?
Yeah, he's all yours, Super Dave.
그래, 네 차지야, 슈퍼 데이브
There was a lot of gasoline over here.
여기에서 휘발유가 다량 검출되네요
Which explains this V-pattern.
V자 모양을 보니 딱이에요
Accelerant, a second point of origin.
촉진제도 있고
여기가 두 번째 발화 지점이에요
Most likely arson.
방화로 보이는데요
Ex-con.
Enemies on the outside...
바깥세상에 적이 있는 전과자에...
two points of origin...
maybe we're looking at a little payback.
발화 지점이 두 군데라...
복수를 하려던 것 같네요
What do you think, Keppler?
어떻게 생각하세요, 케플러?
I think I'd better head back to the body.
난 연구소로 돌아가서
시체를 살펴보는 게 좋겠다는 생각이 드네요
Hey...you know what Grissom
would say here, don't you?
있죠, 그리섬이라면 이럴 때
뭐라고 하셨을지 아세요?
Something ironic, I'm sure.
뭔가 비유하는 말을 하셨겠죠
Looks like somebody
took a staple gun to him.
누가 이 사람한테
스테이플러를 박은 것 같군요
Those aren't bones.
이것들은 다 뼈가 아닐세
That's bad luck, isn't it?
역시 불운이 오는군요
(서양에선 실내에서 우산을 펴면 불행해진다고 함)
싱크편집
송미혜(smh8119@nate.com)
한글번역
신성아(elley@nate.com)
번역수정
정진우(http://www.lifesupport.pe.kr)
한글수정
임재영(dreamimage@nate.com)
월리암 피터슨(길 그리섬 役)
CSI 레벨3(반장), 전문분야: 곤충학
마그 헬겐버거(캐서린 윌로우스 役)
CSI 레벨3, 전문분야: 혈흔 분석
게리 도단(워릭 브라운 役)
CSI 레벨3, 전문분야: 음향/시각 자료분석
조지 이즈(닉 스톡스 役)
CSI 레벨3, 전문분야: 머리카락, 섬유질 분석
조자 폭스(새라 사이들 役)
CSI 레벨3, 전문분야: 물질성분 분석
에릭 스즈맨다(그렉 샌더스 役)
CSI 레벨1, 전문분야: DNA분석
로버트 데이비드 홀(알 로빈스 役)
검시관, 전문분야: 법의학
루이스 롬바드(소피아 커티스 役)
라스베가스 시 경찰청 형사
폴 길포일(짐 브래스 役)
라스베가스 시 경찰청 경감
CSI: Crime Scene Investigation
7x14 Meet Market
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON CBS: 2007/02/1
PVC pipe is sometimes used to place the bones
that have been donated for transplants.
뼈를 제공한 기증자의 몸에
합성수지 파이프를 대신 넣을 때가 있어
So that the body looks right
at open casket? / Right.
관을 열어 놓는 동안 시체를
보기 좋게 하기 위해서 말이죠? / 그렇지
They use umbrellas and
broomsticks for that, too?
그럴 때 우산이랑
빗자루도 사용하나 보죠?
- Not that I've seen.
- Wait a minute,
- 그런 건 처음 보는군
- 잠깐만요
they killed the guy and torched him;
there's no open casket.
사람을 죽이고 불까지 지른 걸 보면
관을 열고 장례를 치르려는 게 아니죠
What's the point of stuffing the body?
시체에 이런 것들을
채워 놓은 이유가 뭘까요?
Looks like the long bones are gone...
긴뼈들이 없어졌고
ditto for the spine...
tendons and cartilage...
등뼈와 힘줄, 연골 조직에다가
most major veins... phew.
주요 정맥들도 대부분
없어진 것 같네요... 얼씨구
They took the heart valves, too.
심장 판막도 가져갔어
So somebody murders an ex-con,
그러니까 전과자를 살해하고
then commits arson to make it
look like an accident
사고처럼 보이려고 방화를 한 다음에
just so that they can harvest
his bones and tissues?
뼈와 조직들을
갈취해 간단 말인가요?
That's big business--
disc replacement,
수입이 짭짤하니까
추간판 이식이나
joint replacement, bypasses,
more demand than supply.
관절 이식, 혈관 이식 등은
공급보다 수요가 많거든
Why leave the kidneys,
the heart and the liver?
그럼 왜 신장이랑
심장, 간은 남겨 뒀을까요?
They're worth big money, too.
그것들도 꽤 짭짤할 텐데 말이죠
Organ donation is heavily regulated.
장기 기증은 규제가 심하지
- Bone and tissue aren't.
- C.O.D.?
- 뼈와 조직들은 널널하고
- 사인은요?
At this point, indeterminate.
지금으로선 확실하지 않아
All I can say right now is based
on the level of decomp,
부패 상태로 봐서는
he's been dead at least a week.
죽은 지 최소한 1주 정도
됐을 거란 것만 확실하네
You think I'm selling body parts?
내가 신체 기관을 판다고요?
Come on, you're wasting your time.
I sell refurbished engines.
시간 낭비하고 계시네
난 엔진이나 다시 팔지
I don't know jack
about body parts.
신체 기관을 파는 것 따윈 몰라요
No one's looking for
a down-and-out ex-con.
무일푼인 전과자를
찾는 사람은 없죠
It's less risky than drugs.
마약 장사보다야
덜 위험할 테죠
I hired Ross to weld metal together.
난 용접 일꾼으로 로스를 고용했어요
Even if I killed him--not saying I did
설령 내가 죽였다 할지라도
내 짓이라고 하지 않을 거니와
but if even if I did, I'd just burn the
body as is, not re-pipe the guy.
내 짓이라 하더라도, 시체 속에
파이프 따윈 넣지 않고 태웠을 겁니다
And I definitely
wouldn't burn him at work.
게다가 내 일터에서 태울 생각은
엄두도 못 냈을 거고요
Fire station's a block away.
소방서가 근처에 있단 말입니다
How do you know Ross?
You meet him in the joint?
로스와 어떻게 알게 됐죠?
감옥에서 만났나요?
I was out before he even went in.
난 로스가 거기 들어가기 전에
출소했어요
I picked Ross up
with a bunch of other guys
헤릭에 있는
큰 철물점 앞에서 일자릴 찾으며
looking for work outside
that big hardware store on Herrick
서성대는 무더기들 속에 있던
로스를 골라 데려왔을 뿐이에요
Four days ago.
그게 4일 전이었죠
When was the last time you saw him?
로스를 마지막으로 본 게 언제죠?
Four days ago.
He'd been working nights.
4일 전에요
밤 근무를 하고 있었죠
Really?
그래요?
'Cause the coroner said
he's been dead at least a week.
검시관 말로는 로스가
죽은 지 적어도 일주일은 됐다는데요
You calling me a liar?
내 말이 거짓말이라는 겁니까?
I'd believe a dead guy
over an ex-con.
난 전과자보다는
시체가 하는 말을 믿거든요
Living large. / Mm.
집이 크네요 / 음
Place this big in MacDonald Ranch--
what's the occupation?
부자 동네에 이렇게 큰 집이라...
집주인 직업이 뭐예요?
That's, uh, Bill Dorton.
You know, Dorton Homes.
빌 도튼이란 사람인데
도튼 건설이라고 알 거야
Biggest homebuilder in town.
거물급 주택 건설 업자지
He built mine.
내 집도 저 사람이 지었어
Oh, uh...
아, 있지...
you'd better throw on some booties.
발싸개를 신는 게 좋을 거야
Margo Dorton, age 39.
마고 도튼, 39세이고
Her husband said he returned from a
business trip and found her like this.
남편이 출장 갔다 돌아와서
이렇게 된 부인을 발견했다는군
No sign of a forced entry.
침입의 흔적은 없어
My guys are gonna go talk to the neighbors,
경관들이 이웃 사람들과 얘기해 볼 건데
see what they say about their relationship.
이 부부 사이가 어땠는지 들어 볼게
What did he say?
남편은 뭐랬는데요?
According to him,
it was a honeymoon every day.
그 사람 말로는
매일 신혼 같았다는군
Maybe...
어쩌면...
she was having a honeymoon
with someone else.
다른 남자와
신혼을 즐기고 있었을지도 몰라
That'll be good motive for the husband.
남편에게는 딱 좋은 동기네
There's a void here.
여기 피가 묻지 않은 부분이 있어
Maybe someone was sitting on the couch,
누가 소파에 앉아 있었거나
or someone was sitting on
the floor in front of the couch.
소파 앞 바닥에 앉아 있었을 거야
But then where's the "someone else"?
그럼 그 '누군가'는
어디에 있는 걸까?
I mean, why kill her and not the lover?
남편이 왜 그 '누구' 말고
부인을 죽였느냐는 말이지
Maybe the husband was the
one having the honeymoon ...
어쩌면 다른 사람과 신혼을
즐기고 있던 건 남편이었고
and the...the wife walks in.
부인이 들어온 거였을지도 몰라
He kills her, tells his lover to beat it.
그래서 남편이 부인을 죽이고
애인더러 도망가라 했겠지
I'd buy it.
그거 괜찮네
Unless the husband's alibi checks out.
남편한테 알리바이가 없다면 말이야
Airport. I was coming
home from the airport.
공항요. 공항에서 왔어요
It's a business trip.
Caught an early flight to surprise Margo.
출장을 갔었는데
마고를 놀라게 해 주려고 일찍 왔죠
I want your best cops on this.
최고 경찰들을 붙여 주십시오
I contributed a lot to this community.
난 이 사회에
공헌을 많이 한 사람이니까요
Absolutely.
Let's establish a timeline.
물론 그래야죠
시간대를 확인해 봅시다
What time did your plane land?
공항에 도착한 게 몇 시였습니까?
Around 10:30. / 10:30.
10시 30분쯤요 / 10시 30분
And you arrived here at... / Midnight.
그리고 여기 도착한 게... / 자정이었죠
Well, it took you an hour and a half at
that time of night to get from McKaren to here?
그럼 맥캐런 공항에서 여기까지
오는 데 한 시간 반이 걸린 거네요?
A half an hour waiting for baggage check,
짐 찾는 데 30분 걸렸고
and half an hour to find my driver,
운전기사 찾는 데 30분
- and a half an hour to get home.
- okay. Alright
- 집까지 오는 데 30분 걸렸죠
- 알겠습니다
Look at this. Valet ticket.
이것 봐. 주차권이야
Nice purse. Nice dress.
멋진 핸드백에 옷도 잘 차려입었어
Maybe safe to say she went out last night.
어젯밤에 외출한 걸로 보이는군
Maybe this will tell us where.
이걸로 어딜 갔는지 알 수 있을 거야
Maybe this...
이걸로는...
will tell us who.
누구와 있었는지도 알 수 있겠는걸
I'm gonna follow a little lead I got.
뭔가 발견했는데 따라가 봐야겠어
Well, I found a circular
blood transfer in the bathroom
욕실에서 지름 7cm 정도로
about three inches in diameter.
둥글게 찍힌 혈흔을 발견했어
- Champagne bottle.
- 샴페인 병이네
- 샴페인 병이야
Looks like it's been wiped down.
깨끗이 닦인 것 같아
Looks like we found
our murder weapon.
살해 무기를 찾은 것 같은걸
So the crispy critter
isn't Ross Neddy?
"로저 라핀스키, 37세로 사망"
불에 탄 남자가
로스 네디가 아니라고요?
- Nope.
- Let me get this straight.
"로저 라핀스키, 37세로 사망"
- 아니에요
- 정리 좀 해 보죠
The ex-con digs up a corpse,
전과자가 시체를 파내고
scoops out a few
body parts to sell,
신체 기관을 빼내서 팔아 버린 다음
then fills it back up
with PVC and umbrellas,
합성수지 파이프와
우산으로 그 속을 채우고
then torches the body where he works
to make it look like he's the victim?
자기가 죽은 것처럼 보이게끔
자기 일터에서 시체를 태웠단 건가요?
Cops don't come looking
for you if you're already dead.
경찰은 이미 죽은 사람을
찾아다니지 않으니까요
If this Lapinsky guy was already dead,
이 라핀스키란 남자가
이미 죽은 거였다면
then how come the doc didn't
find traces of embalming fluid?
어떻게 로빈스 박사님이 방부액
성분을 발견하시지 못했을까요?
He's Jewish. / So what?
- 라핀스키는 유대 인이었으니까요
- 그게 뭐요?
Observant Jews don't believe in
embalming or donating organs.
절실한 유대교 신자는
방부 처리나 장기 기증을 꺼려요
It's part of their faith.
신앙에서 오는 거죠
They think the body should
go out the way it came in.
태어난 그대로 저세상으로
돌아가야 한다고 생각해요
So, this isn't just about
desecration of the body,
그럼, 이게 시신에 대한
모독일 뿐만 아니라
but of the family as well.
그 가족에 대한 모독도 되겠네요
I'll get a court order
for the exhumation.
저는 시체 발굴 영장을
발부받을게요
에이미 맥커티
1969. 6. 28 ~ 1985. 1. 22
당신을 에이미의 추모 미사에 초대합니다
올해는 와 줬으면 했는데
잘 지내게. 앤소니 신부가
What you got?
뭐 나왔어요?
Well, looks like your killer
wigged out on your vic.
범인이 피해자한테서
가발을 벗겨 냈나 봐요
Use the polarizer.
편광 렌즈로 봐요
The pink fiber's modacrylic
with low birefringence.
그 핑크색 섬유는 복굴절 성질이 약하게 있는
수정 아크릴 섬유예요
Most likely made of elura.
아마 일루라 섬유일 거예요
(ELURA : 인조 가발용 소재)
Synthetic hair.
So much for DNA.
인조 모발이군요
그럼 DNA가 넘쳐 나겠어요
And the substance
you found in the toilet--
그리고 화장실에서
채취해 온 그 물질은 말이죠
if it looks like vomit
and smells like vomit, it is.
토사물처럼 보이고 그런
냄새가 나더니만 토사물이더군요
The champagne glasses
were negative for DNA,
샴페인 잔에서는
DNA가 나오질 않았고
and Mandy found nothing but
smears and partials on them.
맨디 말로는 뭉개진 지문이랑
부분 지문밖에 없대요
And the blood from the champagne
bottle just came back to the vic.
샴페인 병에 묻은
혈액은 피해자의 것이었고요
Any good news?
좋은 소식은 없어?
Well, I called the phone
number on the valet stub.
주차권에 적혀 있는
전화번호로 연락해 봤는데
It was a company called Chariot Parking.
셰리엇 주차장이라는 곳이었어요
They operate the parking lots at
30 restaurants and nightclubs.
30개나 되는 레스토랑과
나이트클럽 주차장을 대 준대요
Oh, well, that narrows it down.
범위가 좁혀지는 건 꿈도 못 꾸겠네
Actually, it does.
The ticket on Margo Dorton's key ring
사실은 좁혀졌어요
마고의 열쇠고리에 달린 주차권은
came from a batch
at the Over-Under Cabaret.
'오버언더 카바레'에서
발급한 걸로 나왔거든요
Excuse me, have you seen this man?
잠시만요, 이 남자 보신 적 있습니까?
No. Thank you.
아니라고요. 고맙습니다
Alright, Guys. Listen up!
자, 여러분, 주목하세요!
get ready for tonight's panty auction!
오늘 밤 팬티 경매가 곧 시작됩니다!
Hello. Have you seen this man?
안녕하세요, 이 남자 보신 적 있나요?
- No
- Alright. For our first pair,
- 아뇨
- 자, 첫 번째 상품입니다
starting at the low price of $50,
50달러로 시작하겠습니다
Cotton Candy!
코튼 캔디!
Doesn't accept checks,
just cold, hard cash.
수표는 받지 않습니다
진짜 현찰만 받아요
Check out the pink wig.
핑크색 가발 좀 봐
Bid!
입찰요!
Come on, come on.
Why you got to take the wig?
아, 왜 이래요
내 가발은 왜 가져가는 거예요?
Wig's part of my act.
그건 내 쇼의 일부예요
Y'all are straight stealing
from me right now! Hello!
당신들 내 물건을
훔쳐가고 있는 거라고요! 알겠어요?
- I'm crying for you.
- Synthetic.
- 대신 슬퍼해 드리죠
- 인조 모발이야
Same color and texture as the one
that we collected off the vic.
색깔과 직물 짜임새가
피해자에게서 채취한 것과 같아
Whoa, wh... Hey, hey, hey!
Look, look, look, look, look.
이런, 이봐, 이봐요!
잠깐만요
Look, we didn't even have sex, okay?
우린 섹스는 하지 않았어요
It was all touchy feely.
Jerky treats.
그냥 만지는 것만 했어요
손으로 해 주는 거 있잖아요
What are you talking about?
무슨 말이죠?
The guy I took into V.I.P.
right before panty auction.
팬티 경매가 시작되기 전에
VIP 룸으로 제가 그 남자를 데려갔어요
Look, man, all we did was touch.
이봐요, 그냥 우린
만지기만 했을 뿐이라고요
Why do you think
you're being arrested?
왜 체포되는 거라고 생각합니까?
- Solicitation, right?
- No, actually.
- 매춘 혐의잖아요. 맞죠?
- 아니에요
We found this hair on
this woman's dead body.
여기 이 여자 분 시체에서
이 머리카락이 발견됐거든요
Margo?
마고요?
She's dead?
그 여자 죽었어요?
And you think I killed her?
내가 죽였다는 거예요?
With or without the help
of her husband. / No, no, no.
단독 범행이었거나 마고 남편이
도와줬겠죠 / 아니, 아니에요
Look, man, I never seen
dude in that picture.
이봐요, 난 사진 속
그 남자는 본 적이 없어요
And Margo, yeah, I'll admit,
I slapped the ho around last night,
그리고 마고는... 그래요, 인정하죠
어젯밤 그년을 흠씬 패 주긴 했어요
but I didn't kill her.
하지만 죽이진 않았다고요
You slapped her around?
마고를 때렸다고요?
She's always hanging
out with my fiance, Okay?
그년이 계속
내 약혼자랑 놀아났어요
I couldn't take it anymore, so... yeah.
더는 참을 수가 없어서 그랬죠
Bitch!
망할 년!
Get off of me! / Hey, hey, hey!
저리 가! / 이봐, 이봐!
No!
그만 해!
Why would Margo Dorton
be hanging out here with your fiance?
마고 도튼이 왜 여기서
그쪽 약혼자와 즐겼던 거죠?
- He works upstairs.
- Upstairs?
- 그이는 위층에서 일하거든요
- 위층요?
Look, honey,they don't call this
the Over-Under for nothing, all right?
이봐요, 여기를 왜
'오버언더'라고 부르겠어요?
What's your fiance's name?
약혼자 이름이 뭐죠?
Jesse.
제시요
Take her downtown.
We're going upstairs.
이 여자를 서로 데려가세요
우린 위층에 가 볼 겁니다
Are you serious?
I didn't do anything.
진짜 이럴 거예요?
난 아무 짓도 안 했다니까요
Come on, man.
왜 이래요, 정말
- Is this a restaurant?
- If it is, I'm scared of the menu.
- 여기 레스토랑이야?
- 그렇다면 메뉴가 뭘지 겁나는데
The bus boy looks likes he's in
charge of stocking the champagne.
웨이터가 샴페인 관리
담당인 거 같은데
I'm gonna have a word with him.
내가 얘기를 해 볼게
Okay.
알았어
Would you like a Meet Book
or do you have a steady host?
호스트 목록이 필요하세요
아니면 찾으시는 호스트가 있나요?
Uh, actually, it's my first time.
아, 그게... 처음 왔는데요
What exactly goes on here?
여기가 뭐 하는 곳이죠?
This is a host club,
a place where men entertain women.
호스트 클럽입니다. 남자들이
여자 분들을 대접하는 곳이죠
It's the first of its kind in Las Vegas.
They started in Japan.
라스베가스에서는 최초인데
일본에서 시작된 겁니다
Take your pick.
Hosts get paid by the bottle.
골라 보세요. 호스트들은
샴페인 병 수에 따라 계산됩니다
There's a two bottle minimum.
Bottles range from $50 to $5,000.
최소한 두 병은 시키셔야 하고
가격은 50달러에서 5천 달러죠
What's a $5,000 bottle
of champagne taste like?
5천 달러짜리 샴페인은
어떤 맛이 나나요?
We only sell one brand of champagne.
저희는 한 가지 브랜드의
샴페인만 취급합니다
It's the host attached to the
bottle that determines price.
샴페인에 딸린 호스트에 따라서
가격이 정해지는 겁니다
Everything is legal in Clark County.
클락 카운티에서는
모든 게 합법이군요
Miss, we don't sell sex here.
손님, 여기에서는
성 매매를 하지 않습니다
- What do you sell?
- A relationship.
- 그럼 뭘 파시는 거죠?
- 친밀한 관계죠
Isn't that what most women want?
그게 여성 분들이 원하시는 거 아닙니까?
I don't know.
그건 모르지만
But I know what I want.
I want Jesse.
제가 원하는 건
제시라는 건 알겠네요
Who doesn't?
Let me see if he's avail.
누군들 안 그러겠습니까
가능한지 확인해 보겠습니다
Never seen the old guy before,
but the lady, a bunch.
이 남자 분은 본 적이 없지만
여자 분은 많이 봤어요
Last night, she got blasted on by
one of the strippers downstairs.
어젯밤, 아래층 스트리퍼와
한판 붙었었죠
Really?
그래요?
Are they doing what I think they're doing?
저 사람들 제가 생각하는 걸
하는 거 맞죠?
Hosts get paid by the bottle.
호스트는 샴페인 병 수만큼
수당을 받으니까
So they drink more than
their stomachs can handle.
자기들 위 용량보다
더 많이 마셔서 그래요
Always see blood in those toilets.
호스트들 화장실에선
항상 피가 보일 정도죠
Ah, just off work, huh?
일 끝내고 바로 오셨나 보네요?
Just on, actually.
Sara Sidle, Crime Lab.
사실 지금 시작했죠
과학 수사대 새라 사이들이에요
- What can I do for you?
- Do you know this woman?
- 뭘 도와 드릴까요?
- 이 여자 분 아세요?
Ah. Lady Dorton.
아, 도튼 양요
Yeah, she's one of my relationships.
저와 친밀한 관계를 가진
사람 중 한 분이죠
Could I ask you
a few questions about her?
이분에 대해
몇 가지 여쭤 봐도 될까요?
Okay. Um, I don't like to talk about
my relationships out here.
그러세요. 여기에서
그 얘기를 하는 건 좀 그러니
Let's take it someplace
a little more intimate, yeah?
좀 더 편한 공간으로 가서 하시죠
Okay.
그래요
The coffin had only been in
the ground for about a week.
관이 땅에 묻힌 지는
일주일 정도밖에 안 됐어요
Dirt and sod were pretty loose,
흙이랑 잔디가 듬성듬성해서
so it was relatively easy
to take out and put back in.
비교적 쉽게 꺼냈다가
다시 묻을 수 있겠더라고요
You guys sure do a lot
of exhumations here.
여기서는 시체 발굴 작업을
많이 하나 보군요
As many as we have to.
해야 하는 만큼은 하죠
- Nobody home.
- No surprise.
- 아무도 없군요
- 놀랄 일도 아니죠
Look at this.
이걸 봐요
Lapinsky may have been burned in this shirt,
라핀스키가 이 셔츠를
입은 채로 불에 탔을지는 모르지만
- but I doubt he was buried in it.
- Dead men don't wear plaid.
- 이걸 입고 묻혔을 리는 없어요
- 죽은 사람이 체크무늬 옷을 입지는 않죠
Wait a minute.
Is this blood?
잠깐만요
이거 혈흔인가요?
Dead men don't bleed.
죽은 사람이 피를 흘릴 리도 없죠
How did you meet Margo?
마고를 어떻게 만났죠?
Uh, she picked me from the Meet Book.
그분이 목록에서 저를 고르셨죠
And then what?
그러고는요?
Uh, she wanted what most women want.
대부분 여자들이 원하는 걸
이루고 싶어하셨죠
What's that? No, thank you.
그게 뭔데요?
아니, 괜찮아요
The dream.
꿈요
And that's you. / 50 G's
I make a month says I am.
그게 그쪽이겠죠 / 5만 달러면
제가 한 달 동안 해 드릴 수 있어요
Who doesn't want to be swept off their feet?
그런 걸 열망하지 않는 사람은 없죠
I am not sure it's something
that I would pay for.
그게 돈을 낼 만한
것인지는 모르겠네요
Yeah, but you don't want to spend
your whole life waiting for it either.
그렇긴 하지만, 그걸 기다리면서
평생을 허비하고 싶진 않을 거잖아요
Right here, right now,
a woman can have a relationship
바로 지금, 여기에서
여성은 자신을 기쁘게 해 주려는 남성과
with a man who only wants to please her--
친밀한 관계를 맺을 수 있어요
who can make her laugh,
wipe away her tears,
자신을 웃게 해 주고
눈물을 닦아 주며
give her the confidence to be herself.
자신감을 안겨다 주는 그런 남성과요
And how many of these
relationships do you have?
그런 관계를 가진 사람이
몇 명이나 되나요?
I can handle about 25 at a time.
한 번에 25명 정도는 거뜬해요
Is a woman named
Cotton Candy one of them?
코튼 캔디란 여자도
그중에 한 명인가요?
Yeah. She's been financially
worshipping me for a while.
네, 잠시 동안 저를
재정적으로 흠모하긴 했죠
Now, she says that she is your fiance.
그쪽이 자기 약혼자라 하던데요?
That's good.
Means I'm doing my job.
그거 좋네요
제 일을 잘 하고 있단 뜻이니까요
She told me that she
and Margo had a scuffle.
마고와 난투극을
벌였다고도 하던데요
Yeah. Um... my relationships
do get jealous sometimes,
네, 저와 친밀한 관계를 가진 분들이
가끔 질투를 하기도 해요
especially when one has
more money than the other
특히, 한 분이
자기들보다 돈이 많고
and can monopolize my time.
제 시간을 독점할 수 있는
사람인 경우에는요
Is that why you're here,
because of that little catfight?
그래서 찾아오신 거예요?
사소한 싸움 때문에?
No. Um, Margo Dorton was...
아뇨. 그게...
마고 도튼이...
bludgeoned to death
with a bottle of champagne.
샴페인 병으로 맞아
사망했거든요
Margo was... killed? / Yeah.
마고가... 살해당했다고요? / 네
And you think Cotton Candy killed Margo?
코튼 캔디가 마고를 죽였다는 거예요?
What do you think?
그쪽은 어떻게 생각하는데요?
Um... I wouldn't know.
어... 모르겠네요
Would you know if Margo
took you home the other night?
마고가 밤에 그쪽을
집으로 데려가지는 않았나요?
I don't see my relationships outside of here.
이곳 밖에서는
그 여자 분들을 만나지 않아요
If it does happen, it marks
the end of the relationship.
그런 일이 생기면
관계는 끝이 나니까요
I mean, by having sex with me,
a woman's reached her goal.
저와 섹스를 하고 나면
그 여자는 목표에 도달하는 거예요
There's nothing more I can give her.
그럼 제가 그 여자에게
더 이상 줄 수 있는 게 없게 되죠
Did Margo's husband know about you?
마고의 남편도
당신을 알고 있나요?
She told me she was divorced.
마고가 이혼했다고 했어요
Well, Jesse...
어쨌든, 제시...
I'm, uh, sorry for your loss.
애도의 뜻을 표할게요
I ran the blood from the coffin through CODIS,
관에서 채취한 혈액을
CODIS에 돌려 봤는데
and I got a hit,
but it's not Ross Neddy.
일치하는 게 나왔어요
그런데 로스 네디는 아니에요
So he's got a partner.
그럼 공범이 있단 뜻이군요
Well, DNA matches a Heidi Sultz,
하이디 쏠츠라는 사람인데
who did time for domestic assault
and is currently out on parole.
가정 폭력으로 수감됐었고
지금은 가석방 중이에요
That's funny.
그거 재밌네요
Ross Neddy did time
for domestic assault, too.
로스 네디도
가정 폭력으로 수감됐었거든요
Maybe they're sparring partners.
서로 연습 상대가 돼 줬었나 보군요
This is Heidi's last known.
여기가 하이디의
마지막 거주지로 알려진 곳이에요
According to her P.O.,
she's been trying to straighten out.
착하게 살려 노력하고 있다고
가석방 담당관이 그러더군요
She's detoxed, got a job.
마약을 끊고, 직장도 구하고
She's dumped Ross Neddy.
로스 네디와도 헤어졌다네요
She may be taking the right steps,
but she definitely hasn't cleaned up.
옳은 길로 들어섰지만
완벽히 정화되지는 않았나 보군요
Las Vegas P.D.
라스베가스 경찰입니다
- Heidi Sultz?
- What's going on?
- 하이디 쏠츠 씨?
- 무슨 일이에요?
You're under arrest. / Why?
당신을 체포합니다 / 왜요?
- Where's Ross?
- I haven't seen that dog in weeks.
- 로스는 어디 있죠?
- 그 개자식 몇 주째 못 봤어요
Anyone else living here with you?
같이 사는 사람 있습니까?
Yeah, my baby and
my new boyfriend Charlie.
네, 내 아기와
새 남자 친구 찰리랑 살아요
- Where are they?
- Out back, hanging out.
- 다들 어디 있죠?
- 뒤쪽에서 놀고 있어요
Put her in the car.
경찰차에 태우세요
Ross. Wake up, sugar.
로스, 일어나요, 달링
Hey, baby.
어, 자기야
My name's Charlie, Charlie Keefer.
제 이름은 찰리예요
찰리 키퍼요
Get on the wall.
벽에 뒤돌아서
I got I.D.
It's in my jeans.
신분증도 있어요
청바지 주머니에요
Where'd you get this, the dollar store?
이거 어디서 구했지?
천원샵에서 구했나?
Have a seat, Ross.
앉아, 로스
This is your third strike, pal.
이번이 삼진 아웃이야, 친구
Right now you're looking
at a minimum of 25 years.
지금부터 최소한
25년 형은 맡아 놓은 거지
You want to talk to us?
뭐 할 말 없나?
We can make sure
it doesn't get any worse.
더 이상 나빠질 것도
없을 것 같은데
What do you say?
어디 말해 봐
Daddy will be right there, sweetheart.
아빠 어디 안 가, 아가야
It's ten more for falsifying an ID.
신분증 위조로 10년
Fifteen for grave robbing.
Arson, that's another ten.
도굴로 15년에
방화로 10년 추가되지
Desecrating a corpse, ten;
another 20 for trafficking body parts.
시체 훼손에 10년
신체 기관 밀매로 20년 추가돼
Body parts? No way.
신체 기관요? 그건 아니에요
I thought those cuts were from,
like, an autopsy.
전 수술 자국 같은 게, 아마... 부검 때문에
생긴 거라고 생각했는데요
So you admit to digging
up Roger Lapinsky?
그럼 로저 라핀스키를
파낸 건 시인하는 건가?
I've been out two months
and the best job I can get
두 달 전에 출소해서
얻은 직장이라고는
is five bucks an hour
welding engine parts together.
한 시간에 5달러짜리
엔진 용접공 자리였어요
They wouldn't even let me flip burgers.
햄버거 굽는 일 따위도
시켜 주는 데가 없더란 말입니다
Heidi just had the baby.
하이디가 막 아기도 낳았고요
It wasn't like it was gonna hurt anyone.
누굴 해치려던 건 아니었어요
We dug up someone my age,
제 나이랑 비슷한
시체를 파내서
took him to work.
made him look like me.
직장에 갖다 놓고
저처럼 보이게 만들었죠
And then we torched it.
그다음 불을 질렀어요
All I was looking for was a fresh start.
그저 새 출발 하고 싶었을 뿐이에요
Best way to make it happen was to kill myself.
저 자신을 죽은 걸로
만드는 것만이 최선이었죠
Should've stuck with the five bucks an hour.
5달러짜리 일을
계속하는 게 최선이었지
Who ever did this, must've been pretty angry.
누가 한 짓이건 간에
아주 화가 많이 났던 거야
Let me guess, multiple BFT?
어디 맞춰 보죠
다발성 둔상?
You got it.
맞아
Fractured skull,
broken nose, cheek bones.
두개골 골절에
코뼈와 광대뼈도 부러졌어
Take a look.
이것 봐
Defensive wounds consistent
with a cylindrical object.
방어흔이 원기둥 모양과 일치해
Warrick found a bloody
champagne bottle at the scene.
워릭이 현장에서
피 묻은 샴페인 병을 발견했죠
That'll do the trick.
그렇게 볼 수도 있겠지
But the death blow
came in the neck area.
하지만 치명타는
목 부분에 맞은 거였어
Impacted her Adam's apple
with so much force,
목젖 근처에 강한 충격을 받았지
it sent a reflex arch to the vagus nerve,
그게 반사궁을 통해
미주 신경으로 자극을 전달해서
causing a stimulus to the heart.
심장에 자극을 준 거야
Bradycardia set in,
causing the heart to slow,
서맥이 발생한 거야
심장이 느리게 뛰다 못해
and eventually to stop.
결국엔 멈춰 버렸고 말이야
So where'd you go
after the fight with Margo?
마고와 싸운 다음엔
어디에 있었습니까?
Back to the pole.
무대로 다시 갔죠
You're a real workaholic, huh?
엄청난 일 중독자시군요?
Look, man,the more I work,
더 열심히 일을 해야
the more I can be with Jesse.
제시와 더 지낼 수 있으니까요
I know how hard it is
to wiggle your ass all night.
밤새 엉덩이를 흔들어 대는 게
얼마나 힘든 일인지 알아요
Now, why would you want to spend
all your hard-earned money
그렇게 힘들게 번 돈을 왜
그쪽과 24명의 다른 여자들과
on a guy whose job it is to be
with you and 24 other women?
함께 보내는 일을 하는
남자에게 쏟아 붓는 거죠?
He doesn't care about them.
제시는 다른 여자들에겐 관심 없어요
Now you know this is
not a real relationship.
이게 진짜 친밀한 관계를
갖는 게 아니라는 거 알잖습니까?
It's a business transaction.
그냥 일일 뿐이죠
He's doing the same kind of thing
제시가 하는 일도
that you are doing
on the pole for the guys.
그쪽이 무대 위에서 남자들에게
해 주는 일이랑 똑같은 거예요
Those guys, they can't see
past this, okay?
그 남자들은 내 몸매밖에
보질 못해요. 알겠어요?
I am more than a piece
of meat to Jesse.
제시는 날 그 이상의
존재로 대해 줬죠
He-he-he doesn't judge me.
제시는 날 비난하지 않아요
All right?
He doesn't blow me off.
알겠어요?
날 무시하지 않는다고요
He makes me smile, you know?
날 웃게 만들어 주죠
He heals me,
he heals me when I'm down.
내가 지쳐 있을 때
일으켜 주기도 해요
He makes me feel
like I am Mrs. Steve Wynn.
내가 꼭 스티브 윈 부인인 것처럼
느끼게 해 주죠
(Steve Wynn : 라스베가스 카지노 업계 갑부)
Now we're going to get married, real soon.
우린 곧 결혼할 거예요. 진짜요
Can you show me some verifiable proof
마고가 살해당한 날 밤
of where you were
the night Margo was murdered?
어디에 있었는지
증명할 수 있습니까?
I was in V.I.P. with this pit boss,
카지노 책임자인 손님과
VIP 룸에 있었어요
Joe Brodsky--works at the Olympia.
조 브로드스키라고
올림피아 카지노에서 일하죠
But he's married and
he'll probably deny it.
하지만 유부남이니
그 사실을 부인할 거예요
But I can prove it to you if you
give me my wallet right now.
그래도 내 지갑을 주시면
바로 증명해 보일 수 있어요
Sure. Okay, go ahead.
그럽시다. 이리 줘
There it is.
여기 있다
Right there. He paid me with those.
그거예요. 그 사람이 낸 거예요
Brand-new, straight from the bank.
은행에서 바로 뽑은 새 돈이죠
And what would you like
us to do with those?
이걸로 뭘 하라는 거죠?
You're a CSI.
과학 수사대는 그쪽이잖아요
You can take a print off of there, easy... duh.
거기 지문을 뜨면 되겠네요
쉽기만 한데, 거 참
Hi. What are you doing?
안녕하세요
웬일이세요?
Just looking.
그냥 구경하고 있었어요
- What do you think?
- Meticulous.
- 어떻게 생각하세요?
- 꼼꼼하고...
Obsessive.
강박 관념이 있는 분이네요
Clearly knows his way
around a modeling kit.
모형 제작에 대해
해박한 지식을 갖고 있고요
Grissom didn't make those.
그건 그리섬 반장님이
만든 게 아니에요
No? Hmm.
아니에요? 흠...
Fits the profile.
반장님과 딱 어울리는데요
Bugs in bottles, the Darwin desk set.
병 속의 곤충들과
다윈 책상 세트를 보니까요
He's a bit of a collector of certain things.
뭘 수집하는 취미가 좀 있거든요
Yeah, I knew a guy in Philly like that.
아, 필라델피아에
그런 비슷한 사람이 있어요
Kept a case of thumbs in his closet.
옷장에 엄지손가락을 보관해 두죠
Friend of yours?
친구 분이세요?
No, a serial killer.
아뇨, 연쇄 살인범이에요
Do you miss it? / What?
그리우세요? / 뭐가요?
Philly. / No.
필라델피아요 / 아뇨
Hey, thought you had a deposition.
어라, 증언하러 간 줄 알았는데
Oh, it got postponed.
아, 연기됐어요
So I did a little follow-up on tissue
procurement companies in the area.
그래서 이식용 장기 조달
회사들을 조사해 봤는데요
Turns out there's only two in the state.
네바다에는 딱 두 곳이 있었어요
One is out in Summerlin.
그중 하나는 서머린에 있더군요
It's called Longevity Tissue Services.
이름이 '장수 이식 서비스'예요
Check this out.
이거 보세요
That's the same logo you found on
the umbrella that was in Lapinsky's leg.
라핀스키의 다리에서 나온
우산에 그려져 있는 로고랑 똑같네
Yeah. It's the Chinese character for "long life".
네. '장수'란 뜻을 가진 한자예요
So, what can Longevity do for the L.V. Police?
저희 '장수 이식 서비스'에서
경찰 분들께 어떤 도움을 드릴까요?
We need to know if your
company received tissue or bone
이 회사에서 로저 라핀스키의
신체 조직이나 뼈를
- from a Roger Lapinsky.
- What's the problem?
- 받았는지 알아야겠습니다
- 무슨 문제라도 있습니까?
There might not be one. / All right.
없을 수도 있죠 / 알겠습니다
Well, I'd be happy to check.
기꺼이 확인해 드리죠
Will you excuse me, sweetie?
잠깐 비켜 주겠어?
Yep, there he is.
네, 여기 있군요
Roger Lapinsky, 37 years old,
died of cardiac arrest.
로저 라핀스키, 37세
심장 마비로 사망했네요
It's tragic.
가슴 아픈 일이죠
We're going to need
a copy of his records,
라핀스키의 기록 사본과
and we're going to need
to confiscate his parts.
신체 기관들을 압수해야겠습니다
And if you don't tell me what's going on,
무슨 일로 그러시는지
말씀해 주시지 않으면
you're going to need a warrant.
영장을 받아 오셔야 할 겁니다
This is a criminal investigation.
이건 범죄 수사입니다
Those parts are evidence now.
그 신체 기관들은 이제 증거물이란 거죠
You know, I was always
under the impression
이런 것들은 병원에서나
that the body parts were to be
removed at the hospital.
떼어 내는 거라고 생각했는데요
Major organs have
to be removed at the hospital
주요 장기들은
병원에서 떼어 내서
and then transplanted into the new
patients within four to six hours,
4시간에서 6시간 안에
수혜자에게 이식해야 하지만
but bone and tissue
can be removed at any point
뼈와 신체 조직은
어느 단계에서든 떼어 내서
and stored for up to five years.
5년까지 보관할 수 있습니다
Who gives you access to those parts?
누가 저것들을
제공해 주는 거죠?
I always have signed
consent from next of kin.
저희는 항상 고인 친인척의
동의 서명을 받습니다
And? Most funeral homes
have tissue recovery coordinators.
그리고요? 장례식장마다 대개
조직 적출 조정자가 있어요
They choose who the parts go to.
그 사람들이 그것들을
어디에 보낼지 정하죠
If you have a good reputation,
평판이 좋은 회사일수록
you have a better chance of getting the parts.
받을 확률이 더 높습니다
I help the dead help the living.
전 죽은 자가 산 자를
돕도록 해 주고 있는 겁니다
According to your records,
여기 기록을 보면
Roger Lipinsky's body parts came
from the Silver Hills Mortuary.
로저 라핀스키의 신체 기관은
실버 힐스 장례식장에서 보내졌네요
If that's what it says.
그렇게 쓰여 있다면 그런 거죠
Hey.
나 왔어
So you heard Cotton Candy's alibi checked out?
코튼 캔디의 알리바이가
확인됐다는 거 들었어?
Yeah.
응
And Brass talked to Mr. Dorton's limo driver.
브래스 경감님이 도튼 씨의
운전기사와 얘기해 봤는데
Confirms his story,
he got home way past T.O.D.
사실대로였대
사망 시각이 지나서 도착했다는군
I don't get it, Warrick.
The vic is in a good marriage,
난 이해가 안 돼, 워릭
피해자의 부부 사이는 좋았는데
and she's spending
thousands on a "fake" boyfriend
성 관계를 갖지도 않는
가짜 남자 친구에게
that she's not even having sex with.
수천만 달러를 쓰고 있었다니 말이야
It doesn't make any sense.
들어맞지가 않아
Like this void on the sofa for instance.
소파의 빈 자국도 그래
It suggests the presence of a third person,
제3자가 있었던 것 같은데
but we don't have any evidence to back that up.
그걸 뒷받침할 증거도 없어
Maybe it's not a person.
사람이 아니라
Maybe it's a thing.
물건이 있었던 걸지도 몰라
Rectangular, roughly,
what, 11 by 14 inches?
직사각형에 대충...
28x35cm 정도 되는 게 뭐가 있을까?
It was obviously important
enough that the killer took it.
분명한 건 범인이 가져갈 정도로
중요한 물건이었다는 거야
What if he didn't take it?
범인이 가져간 게 아니라면?
Whose baby is this?
여기 이 아기는 누구죠?
Margo's. / I remember, Bill,
마고의 아기입니다 / 제 기억으로는
you telling me that you didn't have kids.
두 분 사이에 아이가 없다고
하신 것 같은데요
We don't... or I don't.
우리 사이엔 없었어요
나한테는요
She gave him up right after we met.
마고는 날 만나자마자 아기를 포기했죠
She was 17.
And I didn't want any kids.
마고는 17살이었고
난 아이를 원치 않았으니까요
Who'd Margo give the baby to?
부인이 아기를
누구한테 보냈죠?
The biological father,
but he was a drunk.
생부한테 보냈는데
알코올 중독자였어요
Last we heard, the kid ran away.
마지막으로 들은 소식으로는
아이가 가출했다더군요
She was looking at these
photos when she was killed.
부인이 살해당했을 때
이 사진을 보고 있었어요
Yeah.She started taking them out
ever since she hit menopause.
네, 폐경기 이후로 그 사진을
꺼내 보기 시작하더라고요
Wasn't she a little young for menopause?
폐경기가 오기엔
젊은 나이 아닌가요?
They call it premature menopause
and she was having a tough time with it.
병원에서 조기 폐경이라고 하더군요
아내가 많이 힘들어 했어요
The mood swings, the "brain fog,"
the emotional detachment.
감정 기복이 심하고, 정신적
분리 현상인 "혼돈 증상"까지 있었죠
The finality of not having any more children.
더 이상 아이를 가질 수 없게
되어서 그렇게 됐다는 거네요
Bill...
도튼 씨
did you know that Margo was frequenting
부인께서 호스트 클럽이란 곳에
um...a so-called host club,
and paying money to a male escort?
자주 다니시면서 상대 호스트에게
돈을 썼다는 거 알고 계셨습니까?
No. She was paying for sex?
아뇨
아내가 돈을 주고 섹스를 했단 말입니까?
She was paying...for companionship.
돈을 주고 친밀감을 가져왔던 거죠
I'm looking for Salvatore Heinz.
살바토레 하인즈 씨를 찾고 있습니다
You got him.
잘 찾아오셨네요
Mike Keppler, Las Vegas Crime Lab.
라스베가스 범죄 연구소의
마이크 케플러입니다
Sorry if I don't shake.
악수는 사양하겠습니다
I, uh, hope you don't mind
if I keep working here,
작업을 계속해도 될까요?
I'm kind of on a deadline.
제가 사선 (deadline:마감일)에 서 있거든요
That's mortuary humor.
이곳에서 하는 농담입니다
I'm sure it never gets old.
녹슬지 않을 농담이군요
We're following up on a body that
came through here. Roger Lapinsky.
이곳에서 보낸 시체를 조사하고
있는데 로저 라핀스키라고 합니다
You know, he does look familiar.
네, 누군지 알겠네요
I believe he's spending his eternal
rest at Horizon Meadows Cemetery.
호라이즌 메도우 묘지에서
영원한 안식을 보내고 있을 겁니다
Not anymore.
Someone dug him up.
이젠 아닙니다
누가 시신을 파냈거든요
Aw, geez.
아, 이런
You know, sometimes
I wonder what the heck
가끔은 이 망할 놈의 요즘 세상이
is going on with the world these days.
어떻게 돌아가는 건지 모르겠어요
His major bones,
veins and tendons were all stolen.
라핀스키의 큰 뼈와
정맥, 힘줄이 모두 도난당했더군요
Recovered! Not stolen.
'도난'이 아니라 '적출'된 겁니다!
I'm a certified tissue
recovery coordinator.
전 조직 적출 조정자
자격증이 있는 사람입니다
Oh, yeah? That where you learned
how to stuff the bodies with umbrellas?
그러세요? 시체에 우산 따위를
넣는 방법은 어디서 배우셨답니까?
That was a one-time thing.
그건 딱 한 번뿐이었습니다
I ran out of PVC pipe, and, uh...
합성수지 파이프가 떨어져서...
so I improvised. / Understandable.
대용으로 쓴 거였죠 / 알 만하군요
Look, it was a closed casket service, and uh...
관을 닫고 하는 장례였고...
I have a signed consent form.
동의서도 받고 한 겁니다
Where? If you don't mind,
I'd like to take a look at that.
어디에서 말입니까?
그것 좀 보여 주시죠
Sure. Anything for LVPD.
그럽시다. 경찰한테 협조해야죠
I take it you do a lot a work with, uh...
'장수 이식 서비스' 회사와...
Longevity Tissue Services? / Some.
일을 많이 하시는가 보군요 / 조금요
Those are just
promotional items.
그것들은 그냥
판촉물일 뿐이에요
Handy in a pinch, huh?
급할 때 딱이겠네요
Lapinsky, Roger.
라핀스키라... 여기 있군요
- It's all yours. I got copies.
- Thanks.
- 가져가세요. 전 사본이 있으니까요
- 고맙습니다
C.O.D., cardiac arrest.
Everything seems to be in order here.
사인이 심장 마비라...
서류상으로는 문제가 없는 것 같군요
- Like I said.
- Thanks for your time.
- 그렇게 말씀드렸잖습니까
- 시간 내주셔서 고맙습니다
- Keppler.
- Robbins here.
- 케플러입니다
- 로빈스네
Want a C.O.D. on your Frankenstein?
그 프랑켄슈타인의
사인 알려 줄까?
Beat you to it-- cardiac arrest.
알고 있습니다. 심장 마비였죠
Not according to histology.
Roger Lapinsky died of leukemia.
조직학적 소견으로는 아니더군
로저 라핀스키는 백혈병으로 죽었네
You want to repeat that, Doc?
다시 말씀해 주시겠습니까, 박사님?
Sure. Roger Lapinksy died of leukemia.
그러지. 로저 라핀스키는
백혈병으로 죽었네
Thanks.
고맙습니다
If you don't mind, I'll, uh...
괜찮으시다면...
stick around here till the warrant comes.
영장이 발부될 때까지
여기 좀 둘러봐야겠습니다
I got a copy of a Roger lapinsky's
death certificate from Carson City.
카슨 시에서 발부된 로저 라핀스키의
사망 진단서 사본을 입수했어요
This is the one we got from
the mortician, that old nut job, see?
이건 그 늙은 멍청이 장의사한테서
가져온 거고요. 보이죠?
- Changed the C.O.D.
- It turns out, Ty Miloni...
- 사인이 바뀌었어요
- 타이 밀로니에 대해서 알아낸 게 있는데...
is a bit of a hustler as well.
사기꾼 같은 사람이더군요
Those umbrellas were
a promotional gift
이 우산들은 몇 년 전
이 사람이 다녔던
for a vitamin telemarketing
company he ran a few years back.
비타민 전화 판매 회사의
판촉물이었더라고요
This guy isn't even a doctor.
의사도 아니군요
He did drop out of chiropractic school.
척추 지압 대학교도 중퇴했던데요
You're telling me that any Tom, Dick,
그러니까 아무나
or Harry with a sign can
open up a tissue bank?
이런 장기은행을
열 수 있다는 건가요?
Well, if you're FDA registered, yeah.
식약청에 등록되어 있는 사람이면요
How do you get FDA registered?
거기에 어떻게 등록하면 되는데요?
You just fill out a form.
그냥 신청서만 써서 내면 돼요
In the last three years,
37 of the bone and tissue
지난 3년 동안에
실버 힐스 장례식장에서
donors were from Silver Hills mortuary
that went to this Longevity clinic.
이 장수 클리닉으로 보내진
뼈, 장기 기증자가 37구였어요
C.O.D in 23 of those
cases was cardiac arrest.
그중에 23구의 사인은
심장 마비였고요
And most of those decedents
were in their 30s and 40s.
그 기증자들의 연령대는
대부분 30대, 40대였죠
That's a lot of young heart attacks.
심장 마비를 일으키기엔 너무 젊군요
We're going to through all these C.O.D's
이 사인들을
and match them up against the
official death certificates.
공식 사망 진단서와
비교해 봐야겠어요
And do more exhumations.
시체도 더 파내야겠고요
The only thing I'm wondering--
그 장의사가
is the mortician hustling the tissue
bank guy or they're working together.
장기은행 사장한테 사기를 친 건지
둘이 공범인지 그게 궁금하네요
Dr. Stewart, Dr. Klein,
Dr. Combs, Dr. Jones.
스튜어트 박사, 클라인 박사
콤스 박사, 존스 박사
That's not my handwriting.
내 필체가 아닙니다
Well that's the point of forgery,
isn't it, Mr. Heinz?
그래야 위조죠
안 그렇습니까, 하인즈 씨?
A man dies of leukemia,
and his body comes into your mortuary,
백혈병으로 죽은 남자의 시체가
댁의 장례식장으로 들어왔고
and you decide to...sell his spare
parts for a few extra bucks.
당신은 그 신체 일부를
돈 몇 푼 받고 팔려고 했어요
Only problem is, nobody wants
to buy diseased body parts,
그런데 질병이 있었던 신체 기관을
원하는 사람은 없다는 문제가 있었죠
so you make a new death certificate,
change the C.O.D.,
그래서 사인을 바꾼
사망 진단서를 새로 만들고
sign off with a legit doctor's signature,
진단서를 발부한
의사의 이름을 베껴서
and cash a check from Ty Miloni.
타이 밀로니한테서
돈을 받아 낸 겁니다
I'm so disappointed with Mr. Heinz.
He always seemed so honest.
하인즈 씨에게 정말 실망이 크네요
정직해 보였었는데 말이죠
Have you ever followed up
on any of the patients
실버 힐스 장례식장에서 받은 게
누구의 신체 기관인지
who received parts from
the Silver Hills Mortuary?
조사해 본 적은 없으신가요?
No. That's the hospital's job.
But as far as I know,
없습니다. 그건 병원에서
할 일이죠. 제가 아는 한
none of the recipients
have ever complained.
장기를 받은 사람 중에
불평하는 사람은 없었습니다
Maybe that's 'cause
they're not around anymore.
그거야 살아 있는 사람이
없으니까 그랬겠죠
We followed up on several
patients who received Silver Hills
그쪽 클리닉에서 제공한
실버 힐스의 뼈와 조직을 받은
bone and tissue from your clinic
and now seven of them are dead.
환자들을 확인해 봤는데
그중에 7명이 사망했더군요
Three from hepatitis, three from
cancer, and one AIDS-related.
3명은 간염으로, 3명은 암이었고
한 명은 에이즈 합병증으로 사망했어요
The same thing ironically killed the donors.
기증자가 사망한 똑같은 병으로 말이죠
One of those victims was a 15-year-old
healthy high school soccer player.
이식을 받은 사람 중 한 명은
15살의 건강한 고등학교 축구 선수였어요
You gave him a contaminated kneecap.
그쪽에서 감염된 슬개골을 줘서 죽었죠
Oh, my God.
맙소사
He came to me!
그 인간이 날 꾄 거라니까요!
You harvested diseased body parts
and sold them under false pretenses.
병에 걸린 신체 기관을 받아서
거짓으로 팔아넘긴 건 그쪽이에요
He told me what to do.
He... he said it was safe!
그 인간이 시킨 거예요
안전하다고 했단 말입니다!
But you didn't have to do it,
did you, Mr. Heinz?
하지만 거절할 수는
있었잖습니까, 하인즈 씨?
You took money, and people died.
댁은 돈을 챙기고
사람들은 죽었어요
Now, whether or not we
got him--we got you.
그러니, 그 사람이 잡혔든 아니든
댁은 잡힌 겁니다
You've got nothing on me.
I don't care what that...
나한테 뒤집어씌우지 마시죠
그 장의사 놈이 뭐라고 했건
little body snatcher tells you.
난 신경 쓰지도 않으니까요
The families are going to sue you
and your company into bankruptcy.
피해자 가족들이 당신을 고소하면
당신 회사는 파산할 텐데요
They can try.
어디 해 보라 그래요
That is what signed release forms are for.
자필 서약서는 괜히 받은 게 아닙니다
You're reopening a very nasty,
old wound for them, now.
댁은 피해자 가족들의 고통스럽고
오래된 상처에 소금을 뿌리고 있어요
- I didn't do anything.
- Because of you...
- 난 아무 짓도 안 했습니다
- 그쪽 때문에
they're going to have
to rebury their mother,
그 가족들은 자기 어머니나
아버지, 아들딸을
their father, their son, their daughter.
무덤에 다시 묻어야 해요
Ty...let me tell you something.
타이 씨...
한 말씀 드리죠
I'm gonna come down to that clinic...
내가 그 클리닉으로 가서
...and I'm going to go through
it piece by piece by piece.
하나하나 샅샅이 뒤져 볼 겁니다
And if something doesn't jibe,
I can assure you...
만약 맞아떨어지지 않는 게 하나라도 있다면
장담하는데
sir, I will find it.
꼭 찾아내고야 말 겁니다
Well, that is your job, isn't it?
뭐, 그게 그쪽이 하는 일이죠
Yes, it is.
네, 그럼요
And you'll have my full cooperation.
그럼 난 기꺼이 협력해 드리겠습니다
I did a little background on Jesse, the host.
그 호스트 제시 뒷조사를 좀 해 봤는데
He was in and out of 11
different foster homes.
11군데나 되는 위탁 가정을
들락날락했었어
Brass accessed his juvie records.
경감님이 제시의
소년원 기록을 확인해 주셨는데
He had multiple arrests for
prostitution, and drug possession.
매춘이랑 마약 소지죄로
여러 번 체포됐었더라고
Kid had a hard life if he had to take
it to the streets to make a buck.
어린애가 돈 좀 만져 보려고 길거리에서
그런 짓까지 했다니 인생이 험난했겠네
We still need his DNA,
and if he did kill Margo,
제시의 DNA가 필요한데
그 사람이 진짜 마고를 죽였다면
he's not just gonna give it up.
협조해 주지 않을 거야
What about the vomit that we found
in the toilet at the crime scene?
사건 현장 화장실에서 채취한
그 토사물은 어때?
What about it?
그게 뭐?
Well, the hosts drink a lot and throw up a lot.
호스트들이 술을 많이 마신 다음
그만큼 많이 토해 내더라고
Busboy says he always
finds blood in the toilets.
웨이터 말로는 화장실에
항상 피가 묻어 있다고 했어
If Jesse's a host, chances are
he's throwing up blood, too.
제시도 호스트니까
피를 토해 냈을 수도 있잖아
Jesse, we found your DNA
in Margo Dorton's toilet.
제시, 마고 도튼의 화장실에서
그쪽 DNA가 발견됐어요
I thought that you said that you didn't
see your relationships outside of the club.
클럽 밖에서는 손님과 만나지
않는다고 했던 걸로 기억하는데요
Unless, of course,
the relationship is ending.
물론 관계를 끊으면 가능해요
Oh yeah, that's a cold
word for it--for murder.
그거 참 냉혹한 말이군
살인처럼 말이야
I didn't kill her, all right?
전 마고를 죽이지 않았어요
I ended the relationship and I bounced.
Champagne got me sick.
관계를 끝내고 그냥 나왔어요
샴페인 때문에 속이 안 좋았고요
No, I don't think it was the champagne, Jesse.
아니, 샴페인 때문이 아니었을 텐데, 제시
I think it was Margo.
마고 때문이었지
She was coming to see you
for a couple of months,
마고가 몇 달 동안
널 만나러 오면서
spending a lot of money,
돈을 엄청나게 썼어
you were running your pro-game,
you know, doing the host thing.
너는 호스트로서의 네 실력을 발휘했지
Holding her hand, touching, consoling her.
마고의 손을 잡아 주고 만져 주고
슬픔을 달래 주면서 말이야
Laying on the old Jesse magic.
숙련된 제시의 마법을 발휘한 거지
But then she laid some pretty
heavy information on you.
그런데 마고가 너에게
받아들이기 힘든 얘기를 했어
I want you to come home with me.
나랑 같이 집에 가자
So you want to end the relationship?
이 관계를 끝내고 싶으세요?
I guess you thought, you know...
넌 그렇게 생각했겠지
here's Margo, this cougar...
'이 앙큼한 여자가...'
wants to take me back to the love pit,
'이 관계를 끝내고 나와 함께 침대로'
end the relationship.
Sexy time.
'가고 싶어하는구나'라며 말이야
섹스를 말하는 거라 생각했을 거야
But it didn't turn out that way, did it?
하지만 그게 아니었지. 그렇지?
Jesse, I... / Shh...
제시, 난... / 쉬...
Jesse, no. Look, um...
제시, 안 돼. 저기...
I have something I need to show you. Okay?
보여 줄 게 있어. 괜찮지?
This is you.
이게 너야
I'm your mother, Jesse.
내가 네 엄마란다, 제시
I've waited my entire life to tell you this.
이 말을 하는 순간을 평생 기다려 왔어
I love you.
I'm sorry.
사랑해. 그리고 미안해
No!
안 돼!
You look a little pale, Jesse.
Are you getting this?
얼굴이 좀 창백해 보이는군, 제시
이제 생각나나 보지?
She lied to me.
저한테 거짓말을 했어요
Said she hired some private
investigator to find me.
절 찾으려고 사설탐정을
고용했었다고 했죠
Said she'd been building up
the nerve to tell me the truth.
진실을 말할 용기가
생겼다면서 말이에요
Said she had a lot to make up for.
자기 잘못을 만회하겠다고 하더군요
And that, uh...
그러면서...
I could have her car.
자기 차도 주겠다며
And that I didn't have to work anymore.
저더러 더 이상 그 일을
할 필요도 없다고 하더군요
You thought those were lies?
그게 다 거짓말이라고 생각했어요?
Yeah, lies to get closer to me.
네, 저와 가까워지려고 한 거예요
All my clients have their tactics.
고객들은 전부 나름대로의 술수를 부리지만
But hers was... insane.
이건 완전... 미친 거잖아요
She wasn't lying to you, Jesse.
그건 거짓이 아니었어요, 제시
You have 13 alleles in common.
당신과 대립 유전자가
13개 일치해요
You killed your mother.
당신 어머니를 죽인 거예요
Then take me to jail.
그럼 절 감옥에 집어넣으세요
You know, call me a killer...
살인자라고 부르든
a murderer, whatever,
살인마라고 부르든 상관없으니까
but don't tell me I have a mother...
저한테 어머니가 있다는
말은 하지 마세요
because I don't.
없으니까요
I never did.
있었던 적이 없었어요
And I never will.
앞으로도 그럴 거고요
Hey. / Need some help?
안녕하세요 / 도와줘요?
- Aren't you off shift?
- Yeah. Are you?
- 근무 시간 끝나지 않았어요?
- 끝났죠. 닉은요?
Yeah.
저도요
yeah! Thanks.
I'll be back in a minute.
그럼, 부탁해요
금방 올게요
Keppler?
케플러?
자막제작 - 네이트 CSI 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/clubcsi)